好的，你完成了。我给你看看我的解决方案。
All right, you're done. Let me show you my solution.
我们从创建新的空URIMatcher开始，我不希望根节点匹配
We start by creating an empty URIMatcher. I don't want the root node to match
任何东西。这是个习惯。为了使
anything. This is typical behavior. To make the
代码更具有可读性，我将创建一个快捷键
code easier to read, I'm making a shortcut
指向WeatherContract的CONTENT_AUTHORITY。严格意义上，日期
to the WeatherContract.CONTENT_AUTHORITY. Technically, date
一直被认为是数字，但是我
will always be numeric, but I'm matching the
用*，因为它们被存储在
paths with star, because they are stored in
数据库里，以字符串的方式，目的是保持一致。
our database as strings, just to be consistent.
最终，我们有了位置的URI。由于数据库里的ID是
Finally, we have the location URIs. Since the ID in the database is
长整型，用#是非常有意义的。
always a long integer, it makes perfect sense to use the pound sign pattern.
现在我们可以加入我们的类变量了。
Now we can add our class variable.